I want time off. I wanna go on a trip!
I want a dip in the hot springs...!
Pulse-pounding
Hot Springs Gacha!
"Always be facing forward"
Limited Time Only Event
5* Character Drop Rate Up!
One 3* or above
guaranteed
Once Daily
Pull 10
Pull 1
Gacha Details
Member Details
Pull 1 (Paid)
Time off? We just got done with New Year's.
New Year's is over by the time you finish
visiting your family and doing other stuff!
They should extend it!
Simmer down.
You and Katase-san would love to
recuperate in a hot springs too, right?
Under a pristine sky,
surrounded by nature's beauty...
Listening to the chirping of
birds and babbling of rivers,
relaxing as you soak in hot water...
It sounds like paradise for office workers!
She's captured Senpai's heart!
It's not a physical thing.
I need to warm up mentally.
I get you... I really get you, Hayakawa-san!
Maybe they'll have a cat on the premises...
Relief from this jungle of concrete
underneath nothing but blue lights...
No good! Senpai's all the way off
in fantasy land!
Do you seriously wanna go
at the end of the month?
On a weekday, using paid vacation!
That sounds really, really good!
You wanna come, too, Shinozaki?
It'd be kind of weird for me to tag along...
Don't you wanna catch a glimpse of
your senpai, fresh out of the bath?
I just got out of the bath.
I can't deny that, but...
If I take time off, too, work might be...
You should go.
Manager!
We're in a slow period at the moment anyway.
And paid vacation is
meant to be used, after all.
Thank you so much!
In that case, why don't you come, too?
Me?
It'd be a little awkward being the only guy...
That sounds nice! Let's all go together!
I bet it'd be more fun with the whole gang.
Right, Hayakawa-san?
Well, I guess.
All of us, on a trip to the hot springs...
Senpai...
Shinozaki-san...
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
Hayakawa...
Sh-Shinozaki...
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
Hayakawa-san!
Katase-san!
Mm-hm, mm-hm!
This is gonna be awesome!
Hold it!
Can't you be normal about this?!
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
#08 Isn't It Time for Good Boys to Go to Sleep?
What a nice, charming inn!
And we'd normally be
working at a time like this!
Thank you, paid time off!
I'll go get us checked in.
Oh, thanks.
I appreciate you handling
the reservations and the drive, Manager.
No sweat. I enjoy that kind of thing.
Besides, Katase-san
and I shared driving duties.
I was kind of surprised
to find out she can drive.
Maybe I should get my license this year...
Sounds good.
That way, she can
ride shotgun with you next time!
I-I wasn't trying to—
That was Senpai's voice!
The Criminal And
the Hot Springs
Murder Hidden in
the Hot Springs Steam
Mystery of the Hot Springs
D-Did something happen?!
Are you okay, Senpai?!
I'm in fluffy wuffy kitty witty paradise...
It was a scream of joy.
They say you can tell if an inn
is good when it has cats, so...
Nice one, Manager!
Come right this way!
Welcome!
What a complete lack of popularity!
Maybe they're too similar to like her?
So Senpai's a cat?!
Come to think if it, I don't think I've
ever seen her successfully pet a cat...
What do you think, Hayakawa?
You talking to meow, Shinozaki?
A living cat tower?!
Is her body made out of catnip or something?!
I heard this place had a hot springs pool...
But this is pretty huge!
Pretty nice, right?
A pool for the middle of winter!
Let's swim plenty!
I never imagined getting to see Senpai
in a swimsuit in the middle of winter.
Thank you, Manager!
Senpai's swimsuit... Will it be cute?
Or maybe classy?
Or maybe...
Right over here, Katase-san!
Sorry about the wait.
She went with a mature style?!
No good! At the end of the day,
she's my senpai from work!
Gotta stay calm! Restrain those dirty thoughts!
Go with a casual compliment...
You both look wonderful.
Thank you.
Thanks...
Manager!
That was flawless, and he made it look easy!
What do I even say?!
You really does look nice...
Chickening out with a safe approach
Th-Thank you...
She covered up?!
I-I suddenly feel really self-conscious!
I can't believe we're at the pool and I
don't get to see Senpai in a bathing suit...
Maybe I should just ask her to show it to me?
No, that'd be sexual harassment.
Come to think of it,
what's with the inner tube?
I bought it just now.
You work fast.
Okay, Manager, let's head
to the river pool with that inner tube.
Sounds good!
The river pool...?
Come on, then!
Sure!
That's right! If we get in the pool,
I'll naturally get to see the swimsuit!
IQ reduced to 3 by impure thoughts
Good job, Hayakawa!
Senpai, come on!
You all can go on and have fun.
She must really not want me to look at her...
The problem is that I can't swim!
Th-Then maybe the wave pool...
You all can go on ahead.
The kiddie pool...?
Go on.
Senpai, can you not swim?
It's not that I can't.
It's just that I never have before!
That would mean that you can't, wouldn't it?
S-Sorry! I shouldn't make fun.
I want ice cream!
Let's go ask dad, then.
When I was little...
I went into the deep end of the pool,
lost my footing, and almost drowned...
I've had trouble with it ever since.
Round and around and around—
I do think that it looks like fun, but...
Manager, slow down!
In that case, do you want to go in together?
I'm tall enough that I can stand on the bottom,
and we can watch out for each other.
I'll give it a try.
This is warmer than I imagined.
Are you scared?
Not at all!
I almost feel like I could
start swimming already!
What's wrong, Shinozaki-san?!
Nothing.
She's trying so hard!
Cast out those wicked thoughts, me!
Well...
Could you teach me how to swim now?
Is this gonna work?
For starters,
try putting your face into the water.
Got it! Watch me! Here I go!
She might actually figure this out quickly—
Or not!
I can normally put my face underwater
with no problem... What's going on?
You're probably nervous
because of the location.
Maybe if you imagine
you're in the bath, it'll be easier.
The bath, the bath, the bath...
She's acting like a cat that hates bathing!
Maybe submerging your face
is a little too much to start with.
Sorry...
It's okay. Let's start with an inner tube
and have you practice swimming.
I'll go buy one.
Shinozaki-san?
Not good! I've got a cramp.
I got careless because the water's so shallow!
Someone... help...
S-Senpai?
Senpa—
Live!
I-I'm okay! I'm alive!
How are you feeling?
All good.
Thank goodness...
I thought you might die.
No, it's okay! I'm feeling great!
Don't worry! You can relax!
Okay.
More importantly, Senpai...
You just swam.
Oh, come on! That's not more important!
S-Sorry...
Huh... dizzy...
Had I not caught my breath yet?...
I-I can't fall...
Th...
This is bad!
Safe!
L-Let me retie that for you.
Yeah...
There.
Sneak...
Nobody saw that, right?
Um...
I'm so sorry! I don't know
how to make it up to you!
Is that all you have to say?
D-Do you want me to bow?!
Or maybe a written apology?!
Never mind, then.
Sulk...
S-Senpai?!
My Tiny Senpai.
I took a dip in the baths already.
Oooh, that hits the spot...
I can feel the exhaustion washing away.
Christmas, the end of the year,
and then New Year's...
I think Japan might cram too many
events into such small a window.
Maybe.
But I do feel really refreshed after today.
Thank you for inviting me, Hayakawa-san.
No, thanks for coming.
If it was just me,
I would've probably just whined about wanting
to go and never actually done anything.
And I definitely wouldn't have done
anything as active as playing in the pool.
I guess so. It's been a long time since
I've worn a swimsuit, too. It was fun.
It was fun, but...
I feel like I've embarrassed myself a bit, too.
I need to regain my honor
as a senpai before bedtime!
Shinozaki-san!
Say "ahhh."
Wh-Wh-Whoa, Senpai!
Okay, who gave Senpai booze?!
Come on, come on, "ahhh!"
No one at all.
No one stopped her, either, though.
Maybe you should have?!
Don't you remember
what happened with the chocolates before?!
Hayakawa-shan!
Smooch!
I am so, so grateful!
I guess that was a thing! Must've forgot.
I seriously doubt you forgot.
Oh, man, my drink...
Oh, dear!
Let me wipe that up.
I-It's okay! I can handle it!
No...
Today, until bed...
Senpai is gonna take care of everything.
No, it's s-s-seriously fine!
Do you have an upset tummy?
I can rub it for you.
That's okay!
Don't be shy now, come on...
What's going on?!
What kind of drunken behavior is this?!
Does your tummy hurt?
I'm telling you, it's fine!
Does Katase-san get
more intense when she's drunk?
Please stop! You can't! This is... too much!
Seems like it.
Earlier, in the bath...
I'm really fine!
I need to regain my honor
as a senpai before bedtime!
After what she said...
Maybe that's why.
I don't see what she has to
make up for in the first place.
Turn this way!
She probably just wants to show off a little,
as your senpai.
Okay, Shinozaki-san, let's wipe that mouth!
I have to admit, this situation...
It's nice, but it's so awkward!
Hayakawa! Help!
Sorry, Shinozaki.
I'm feeling like another dip in
the open air bath, since we're here.
Oh, me, too.
See ya!
Traitors!
Shinozaki-san, say "ahhh" again...
I'm alone with Senpai
when she's acting like this?!
In that case...
I'll play along to the end
so she can go to bed satisfied!
Tastes good?
Tastes good...
After dinner comes brushing teeth!
I can't brush them like this.
Right over here.
O-O-On your lap?!
Does it hurt anywhere?
Nope.
Come forth, all of my restraint!
Once we're done, you'll go
goosh goosh with your mouth.
That onomatopoeia sounds kind of dirty!
What a nice brushing! Clap clap clap!
As nice as this is... I can't take much more...
At this point, I just want to go to bed.
Are you sweepy, Shinozaki-san?
Uh, well...
In that case...
Senpai will put you to bed.
I-I can't sleep yet!
That's no good. No staying up late!
Isn't it time for good boys to go to sleep?
There is no chance I'm sleeping!
Huh, that's weird.
I was sure I brought it with me...
She forgot something?!
Oh, crap...
If they show up now,
it's gonna be really annoying!
We'll celebrate with red bean breakfast!
Hello, Onee-san?
What?! They're getting married?
I need to avoid that at all costs!
Shinozaki?
Weird, the lights are off.
And they're both gone...
I wonder if they went out.
We didn't run into them in the halls, either.
I hid without thinking!
But if she forgot something,
they'll probably leave soon...
Find it?
This is so weird...
I thought I put it in here.
The baths are separate anyway.
You can go on without me, Manager.
I'll wait. You can take your time.
You can't take your time!
Crap...
Did you say something?
Not me.
I thought I heard a voice.
Was it from outside?
I think it was from in the closet...
Oh, no, no, no!
It's your special Senpai heating pad!
S-Senpai?!
Is it warm?
Yes, incredibly...
Wait, heating pad?!
That's right. Sneezing and sweating...
You definitely need warming up.
It really is coming from in there...
Oh, no!
Senpai heating pad!
W-W-Wait, now's not the time! Please, let go!
It's an adhesive, and not going anywhere!
Feeling warm?
Crap, crap, crap!
Senpai... please, quiet down for a sec.
Maybe you're imagining it.
I guess.
We're saved...
Shinozaki-san...
Your hand...
Your hand's on my chest.
Did you hear that?
Yeah...
Come to think of it,
a long time ago, this inn was where—
Stop it right now!
We were enjoying this trip together...
Wait, is the reason
they're missing because of ghosts?!
We can't rule that out.
Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
Call the police?! An exorcist?!
W-We need to find them, either way!
Hayakawa-san, calm down!
That voice... Hayakawa-shan?
Hayakawa-shan! I'm right here!
Senpai's going out!
What do I do, what do I do?!
Hayakawa... san...
H-Huh? It's all dark...
Help!
Hayakawa-san! Wait up!
We managed to avoid being found...
She's asleep.
I guess that wraps this up... I hope.
Shinozaki-san...
Are you okay?
Senpai, you're gonna catch a cold like that.
Let's get you in a futon.
'Kay...
She was worried about
how she came across before...
But I'm glad I got to see
a different side of you, Senpai.
Her hands...
She won't let go...
Oh, this is really bad!
Right this way!
There's a ghost in this room!
Hello, Onee-san?
Prepare some red beans and rice.
I see. A wedding it is.
Stop!
Oh, what a glorious day!
Uh, look, this is actually—
Where's the ghost? Where'd it go?
Senpai, could you wake up
and help me explain? Please...
I better look into venues...
Wait, what was going on?
Oh, I actually know someone
who can help with that.
And I'll be aiding
with dress selection, of course.
So much fun...
You've got it all wrong!
Bleary-eyed and not fully awake from a dream
I still can't bring myself
to drink that bitter coffee
So I sneakily toss in
two pinches of a sweet secret
And let it slowly spread throughout
There's a local bakery
that's only open sometimes
Where I once had some toast that glittered
What is it that makes it so satisfying?
Almost like magic
I find myself thinking about that kind of thing
How the small things can be the most precious
Deep inside my heart
It's ever so bittersweet
"Just being around you is enough"
Becomes my mantra
Baby like sugar
Baby you're the sugar